Let me just say this. You want to be the beneficiary.
No other title actually matters
because equity sees the beneficiary as the true owner of the trust,
not trustee, not executor, beneficiary.
There are two parties I wanna focus on,
trust and estates. The estate gets charged, right,
and the trust settles the charges, right?
You are the beneficiary, meaning
the trust works in your favour
to stop you from being held as surety for charges against the estate.
This is why the trust is so important.
It stops you from paying debt that are not your responsibility.
Because if there's no money and we've been in bankruptcy since 1933,
all we have to do is accept the charges against the estate
and discharge them in trust.
So can we please live like we know what to do in 2026?